Protecting your family is your first
priority. ICC Lombard
offers the perfect plan for you. The Family Seal
plan is comprehensive, flexible, and unique. It
offers more for your protection.
Some of the key features of this plan are:
Infectious Disease Benefit, Personal Accident Benefit,
Flexibility,
Family Policy Term and Renewal Benefit.
Infectious Disease Benefit can be very helpful
as various diseases have become more common now.
It provides coverage against specific vector-borne diseases like rabies
and tetanus,
gastrointestinal infections, viral and
otitis media. Personal Accident Benefit
is an important factor for protection.
It covers death and disability, accidental death,
broken bones, and children's education grant.
This plan provides you with what
you need. You
can opt for one or more complimentary benefits under a single policy. If the premium is
paid, you will be eligible for the basic benefit
or extension.
Several add-ons are also available for the policy. This
plan also offers you a term and renewal benefit.
You can
get a policy term of up to 3 years with a long-term discount.
You also get a five percent renewal
discount.  Must be paid on
or before the policy expiry date or within 30 days both. Not only this,
you also get a family policy premium of up to 7.5%.
Give your family the protection
they deserve and give yourself a
hassle-free claim experience.
With ICC Lombard's Family Insurance Plan, you are
our priority.